很好，你完成了。我们来看看答案
Alright, you're done. Lets take a look at the solution.
现在我们需要一些TextViews。首先
Now we're going to need some text views. First of all lets
让我们看看LinearLayout。这是垂直的。我们希望它是
look at our linear layout. It's vertical. We're going to want it
水平的。接下来我们需要
to be horizontal. The next thing we're going to want are a
很多TextViews。把它们拖进来就好。
bunch of text views. Lets just drag them in. Now
在上一个测试里我们创建了一些ID
remember we had all those ID's that were given to us
第一个是list_item_date_textview
in the last quiz. The first one is the list_item_date_textview
我们会写一些文字
And we'll give it some text that makes
这会帮助我们创建这个界面
sense when we help to layout the layout. We'll remove
我们会在真正提交前删掉这些文字的
this before we actually submit it to our project. And
我们可以把屏幕横过来玩玩。这会看起来
for fun let's switch to landscape. It'll make things a
更清晰些。然后我们再放大一点点
little more legible. Also let's just zoom in a little bit.
很好，这就是我们的list_item_date_textview。接下来
All right. So that's our list item date text view. Now
我们需要另一个TextView。因为我们想要外观设计保持一致
right next to that, we want another text view. Since we want the design to be
这一个不需要一个ID。如果你还记得
the same, this one doesn't need to have an ID. If you remember our
我们的设计是一个日期，接着一个短横线，
design had the date. Followed by a dash, followed
接着是预测温度，然后是一个短横线，然后是最高温度
by the forecast, followed by a dash, followed by the high,
和最低温度中间被斜线隔开。所以这个TextView只需要
followed by a slash, followed by low. So this is just going to be a view that
有一条短横线。我们甚至可以暂时把它写死在程序里。然后我们
contains a dash. And we can even hardcode this in. For now, then we're going to
要在旁边创建另一个TextView
create another text view next to that. Our
这个地方会显示一个天气预报，比如Clear
placeholder text will be a forecast, like clear.
这个的ID是list_item_forecast_textview
The ID for this will be list item
现在我们需要另外一个TextView
forecast text view. Now we need another text view.
再说一次，这个TextView不需要ID，因为用不着。
Once again this one's not going to have an ID, because we don't need it. And
然后加上另一条短横线。现在我们开始做
we'll add another dash. Now we're actually getting
最高和最低温度。假设
to the high and low forecasts. Let's say
最高温度23.接着是一个画斜线的TextView，
a high of 23. One more plain text view, this one with a slash and, once
不需要ID.最高温度的ID
again, with no ID. And for our high
最好是list_item_high_textview。最后我们再加
forecast, it better be list_item_high_textview. Finally, we'll add one
一个空白的TextView。这一个是用来显示
more plain text view. This one will be for
最低温度的。很明显，它的ID是
our low, and of course, that means it's going to
list_item_low_textview。这就是我们做的多个TextView
be list_item_low_textview. And there we have it. Our multiple text
的界面。我们可能会想把它做得更漂亮点
view layout. Now we might want to make this prettier.
但是这是一个很好的开始，并且刚好具备了
But this is a good start and it just plays
我们要求的四个部分。它们全都是
the four fields that we asked for. They are all
LinearLayout的一部分。在我们提交这个代码前
part of a linear layout. Before we actually would submit
删除掉所有的备注信息，除了
this, lets remove the placeholder tabs for everything except for,
这些静态文字。我们还要删除掉这些空ID，
the static fields. We'll also have to remove these empty IDs, its
实际上这对于帮助我们理解这些TextView是很重要的。
actually important to understand whats going on in these text views. And there
删完了，这就是你的界面看起来应该有的样子。至少如果你
we have it, that's what your layout should look like, At least if you
希望它看起来和我们刚开始看到的一样
want to make it look almost identical to the layout we started out
当然你可以自由发挥
with. Of course you can go wild with these designs, and there's
用这个界面编辑器和各种不同的Layout，你可以做很多事情
a lot you can do with the layout editor and with different kinds
我们会在下一节课学到更多。好了
of layouts. We'll be learning more about that in the next lesson. Alright,
我们终于开始跟用户体验联系起来了。让我们
we finally get to start hooking this up to our UX. Let's go
回到ForecaseFragment
back to forecast fragment.